ALES Course Materials 5225 C
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ALES Course Materials
1922-1949
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
American Labor Education Service (ALES)
5225 C
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8209446
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
A. Holland-Loucks, August 02, 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 21, 2017
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5225: ALES Records 5225 E: ALES Labor Education Records 5225 I: ALES International Labor Records 5225 L: ALES Labor Plays 5225 S: ALES Scrapbooks 5225 MB: ALES Pearl L. Willen Memorial Memorabilia
American Labor Education Service
8209446
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  More documents. Syllabi, notes, etc. in Economics, History, English, Psychology.
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers in Industry, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School, 1922-1924 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School, 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bryn Mawr Summer College, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School, 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bryn Mawr Summer College, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Bryn Mawr Summer College for Women Workers, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Women Workers, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School for Worker Women, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Bryn Mawr Summer College for Worker Women, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Vineyard Shore Worker School, 1929-1938 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Shop and School Summer School, 1931-1937 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Scrapbooks (Southern Summer School; Little Switzerland, N.C.) Shop & School (Bryn Mawr Summer School), 1931-1935 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Vineyard Shore School (Scrapbook and Short Play), 1933 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Scrapbooks (Southern Summer School for Workers), 1936-1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Classroom Documents - Bernard Summer School, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Classroom Documents - Bernard Summer School, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Barnard Summer School - Classroom Documents, 1930-1932 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Documents - Bryn Mawr Summer College for Workers, 1929-1930 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Barnard Summer School for Women Workers, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Univ. of Wisconsin Summer School for Workers in Industry, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Presentations from the Southern Summer School for Women Workers, 1929-1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Affiliated Schools for Workers, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Affiliated School for Workers, Inc., 1932-1947 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Documents on Labor Movements (Italian and Russian) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Part of the Lectures on Economics for Brookword
- Documents on Labor Monents (Russia, Italian) (Lectures for Brookwood Courses in Econ.), 1926-1934 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Documents from the Affiliated Schools for Workers, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Documents from the Affiliated Schools for Workers (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Documents on Trade Unionism and the Labor Movement, 1930-1938 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Documents on Trade Unionism and the Labor Movement (Box 3, Folder 4)
- "Union Administration and Leadership" Course Documents (@ Uchicago), 1949 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- "Union Administration and Leadership" Course Documents (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Course taught at the University of Chicago
- Reports by Affiliated Schools for Workers, 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Reports by Affiliated Schools for Workers (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Newprints of the American Labor Education Services, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Newsprints of the American Labor Education Service (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Documents on Workers' Education (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Documents on Workers' Education, 1938-1945 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Workers' Education Booklets (Lots of them) (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Worker's Education Booklets (Lots of them), 1924-1933 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- American Labor Education Association - Bulletin, 1936-1947 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- American Labor Education Association - Bulletins (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Bibliographies and Suggested Reading on the American Labor Movement (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Bibliographies and Suggested Reaching on the Amer. Labor Mvt., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- American Labor Education Services Conference reports (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Amer. Labor Education Services Conference Reports, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- WPA - Work Projects Administration, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- WPA - Work Projects Administration (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Publications and Supplementary Reading, 1931-1934 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Publications and Supplementary Readings (Box 3, Folder 14)
- American Labor Education Service Reports (Box 3, Folder 15)
  1934-1946
- American Labor Education Service Reports, 1933-1946 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Summer School for Women Workers' Documents, White Collar Worker pamphlets, Reports, and Reprints (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Summer School for Women Workers White Collar Worker Pamphlet, 1938-1947 (Box 3, Folder 16)